JAN MICHAEL CAASI

JUNIOR DEVELOPER WEB





+639997543046



janmichaelcaasi@gmail.com



San Mateo, Rizal



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jancaasi-53ab30277/

LINKS

Portfolio: https://portfolio-v2-

xcmy.onrender.com

Github: https://github.com/jantoy052003

SKILLS

- Front-End
 - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Tailwind, Bootstrap
- Back-End
 - o PHP. Laravel
- Database
 - MySQL
- Collaboration Tools
 - o Github, Jira, Confluence, Teams, Slack, Google Meet Zoom, MS Office, Canva
- · Team player and a leader
- · Critical thinker
- · Able to multi-task
- · Results-oriented

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN COMMUNICATION (Undergraduate)

University of the Philippines Baguio 2003-2006

PROFILE

To carry through the goals of a Full-stack Web Developer and to be globally competitive to further strengthen my skills and knowledge by working with great sense of responsibility, dedication and hard work, such that, whatever expertise, training or skills I gain will be used for development and share in the further growth of the company.

EXPERIENCE

QA ENGINEER INTERN

D.W. Morgan

2023 - 2024

- · Created and maintained test cases for project assignment
- Assisted web and mobile developers in testing applications before scheduled deployments
- Effectively tracked problem reports or tickets on Jira and followed through on the progress

KODEGO BOOTCAMP GRADUATE

KodeGo

2023

· Built three outstanding website projects as part of training requirement, two of which are with a team:

Serendipity Villa website

March 6 - March 16, 2023

- Tools used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- Individual project that I built from the ground up

MP2 Movie trailers

March 27 - April 11, 2023

- o Tools used: ReactJS, Bootstrap, JSON database
- Built the database from scratch and collaborated with my partner in building the Frontend UI

Mindfulltasks web app

April 26 - May 12, 2023

- Tools used: ReactJS, Tailwind, Laravel, PHP
- Built a task reminder/organizer web app from scratch
- Led a team of three in concept building and design, provided Backend codes and some Frontend UIs, presented the project to a team of panelists, and won us the best capstone project

TIER 2 TECHNICAL SUPPORT ADVISOR

TDCX Philippines

2020-2022

- Handled Tier 1 escalation cases and consults as a Tier 2 technical support advisor for Apple
- Hand picked by management to be part of mentoring team who assisted and taught new employees and Tier 2 advisors.